psprint.com 2013-11-27

# Learn the privacy policy of online printing company PsPrint.

[_PsPrint.com_](http://www.psprint.com/) is committed to maintaining the confidentiality of our customers. We do not share, sell, or otherwise disclose information about our customers to any other party except as required to process and ship purchases. This privacy statement only applies to [ www.psprint.com](http://www.psprint.com/). This privacy policy describes how PsPrint.com ("PsPrint," "we," "us," "our") collects and uses the information you provide on our site. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information relating to your business and how you can access and update this information. 

Information Collection

PsPrint is the sole owner of the information collected on _[http://www.psprint.com](http://www.psprint.com/)_. PsPrint collects information from our users at several different points on our site.  
We use this information to fulfill your order, send you requested product or service information, respond to customer service requests, send you marketing communications, administer contests surveys or sweepstakes you may have entered, and improve the customer experience while on our site.   
We reserve the right to disclose information about you as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our site.   
We may purchase additional data about our customers from third party sources and combine it with the information we have already collected in order to assist us with our marketing activities.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. PsPrint does not store this information after sending this one-time email. 

Registration

In order to use My PsPrint, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give a name and email address. We use this information to contact the user about our services even if they have not placed an order.

Communications from the Site

Special Offers and Updates:  
Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. If you do not wish to receive future emails, please see the Choice/Opt-out section below.

Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services. Both our production and customer service staff use email and phone information to communicate with customers about issues pertaining to their orders.

Social Media

Our site includes social media features such as Facebook "Like" and "Share This" buttons. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

Blog and Testimonials 

Our site offers a publicly accessible blog. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. 

With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us via one of the methods listed below. 

Cookies and Other Technologies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use persistent cookies. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

Cookies are used by both the My PsPrint and the PsPrint order section in order to uniquely identify users, associate user files with orders, and to enable the shopping basket. Our site cannot be used with cookies turned off. 

Some of our business partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site to help us manage the content on our site as well as to manage our advertising on other sites. These technologies are used to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. The information gathered by web beacons is not tied to our customers' personally identifiable information. We have no access to or control over these technologies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by PsPrint only and does not cover the use of cookies or web beacons by any third parties. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by [clicking here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). 

Log Files

Like most standard website servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This data is not linked to personally identifiable information.

Security

We are committed to protecting your information. Security measures are in place on this site to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We offer industry-standard security measures available through your web browser. When you are on this site, the sensitive information you provide such as credit card and financial information is encrypted with secure socket layer (SSL) technology and scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches us. Please remember that e-mail, which is different from the encrypted sessions above, is not secure. Therefore, we ask that you do not send sensitive information such as credit card or account numbers to us via an unsecured e-mail message.

Information Disclosure and Your Choices

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, an email service provider to submit email communications to you on our behalf, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

If PsPrint should go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information is to be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section. 

Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email, emailing us at [remove@psprint.com](mailto:remove@psprint.com) or by following the unsubscribe instructions within the email. 

Links

Our site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site. 

Notification of Changes

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement on the homepage and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If we are going to use users' personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will post a prominent notice on our site notifying users prior to the change becoming effective.

If customers have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. 

Access to Correct/Update/Deactivate

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, or request that it be deleted/deactivated by accessing your My PsPrint account or by contacting us at the address listed in the Contact Information section.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [privacyprogramoffice@deluxe.com](mailto:privacyprogramoffice@deluxe.com). For all other requests, please contact us at:

Customer Service  
PsPrint.com  
2861 Mandela Parkway  
Oakland, CA 94608  
800.511.2009

TRUSTe Privacy Program

PsPrint has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [ TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only the information collected on the PsPrint Web site.

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions _._ If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at privacyprogramoffice@deluxe.com _._ If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [ TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).
